<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Barbras Book</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank NEWS !fragment</string>
    <string name="dummy_article">
     \t Barbra Streisand calls for end to \'antiquated\' Electoral College
    Trump\'s vindictive pettiness renders him incapable of taking the high road
    Ocasio-Cortez: If male politicians could get pregnant, there\'d be as many Planned Parenthood clinics as post offices
    is calling the Electoral College an "assault on our democratic principles," saying it\’s time for the institution to end.
    \n
    The Academy Award winner is one of several high-profile public figures — including House Speaker Nancy Pelosi (D-Calif.) and Rep. Elise Stefanik (R-N.Y.) — who contributed to a piece in The Washington Post published Wednesday on what the Constitution means to them.
    "The 14th Amendment of our Constitution actualized what many of the Founders wanted, promoting equal protection under the law for all Americans," Streisand, 77, said.
    "If I could, I would end the antiquated electoral college," added the singer and actress, a prominent Democratic donor and frequent critic of President Trump.
    "Twice in the last 20 years the popular vote winner was denied the presidency," wrote Streisand.
    \n
    "This is an assault on our democratic principles, where the dictum should hold true: one person, one vote," she added.
    It\'s not the first time Streisand has railed against the Electoral College. In 2016, she shared on a "suggested reading" page on her website a New York Times article questioning why it endures despite being "hated by many."
    Streisand, a Hillary Clinton supporter in the 2016 White House race, said during an interview last year that the former Democratic presidential nominee "got 2.9 million votes more than Trump and she\'s not the president. So I don't know. This antiquated Electoral College doesn\’t sit well with me. It\’s not fair. I think the people should vote for who the leader is of our country.</string>
</resources>
